hi so we start I just wanted to give you
an update before via unfuckin Michigan
you were an actor and stand-in for me it
gets cool
Eva clouds dusty and the beauty connect
with / - with he feels and sera knee
who's been taking care of I mean II feel
the SIS special in Kosovo class and feel
like this is the guy in the glass and
anything seoeon so but believe me
everything is fine particular alice's
school trust assure that I felt strongly
the other day stark a filter a crashing
moment thus the soul
so I van cynic a moment fondle fun just
fun impermanence this we have miss
Barrett's and SK don't VMs and spirit
may be truly helped us assign additions
like she owned and Dion's Jesus my
Gilead gunsmiths on that would be the
antidote for us
Thomas is the sanatorium atone Chris
take a short meditation five-minute
meditation on democracy ina film
initiated at soon the choice in bring
cash in my case wound upon a designer
and not for the sanctimonious academic
session of the Leon is given a so
primarily and in academia she Bernardo
twice a scientific first enter Smith on
so tile mitten by schmidtty shifter so
that's right thank an ID wound upon
kishankant he owns in inlets in Syntagma
gave mahant it's a source gross what's
behind is main tried a few just about
the last 10 days hear me i'm foraminal
think about site name is and instead of
a freud was such near
so a home must consume it nach Hause in
a minute item guys Dinah my hats because
Roy sky here many cabbies you are not
that's what st. are just decent grunt
abort rate but I think it would be a
gift to him Java is very angry shame the
city said harming all Olivia Alex Osama
need this is cashing the sphere Berkeley
behalf Berkeley steed chief Universal
recipient Lanham on Vitas on Jerry Lee
sefa pasado de belem see professor on
the court excite your beautiful seeds
Buddha ban some and Ferguson tied
achievement we can always that's
astonishing the sphere Emma gave us a
praxis eccentric astonishing so we're at
the final ACI class let's say I write
quickly read through my notes and notes
on all the points or geshe-la heart
occasionally book their names to
re-emphasize them the purpose of the
class but we covered many of the points
this content of Maha before any Bush I
enjoyed to desuka impose okay and so in
the process of the correct view what is
correct view was this correct deceased
mark mark mark did it he just had to do
this we markets mock Dumas member notice
a hunter vehicle mock first in v8
against in the sea things I mean
actually the principle is to see that
things are coming from you to electing a
40 motif the school - let's come to
India and we understand this idea
correct of the two realities we we know
the pen this is simple honest reality
should DCI or when you teach in a CAC
combat for where the puppy comes into
the room just another moment we say in
DCI language whose right bra hi sister
Beatrice just anxious
the motor is essential so excited
usually people get and say well both are
right reality exists but the spice house
will toil for nebari may transfer to
first in the sky survives the reality
that even on the exist here in the gun
sits on what about other realms you know
we know these rooms exist disability
exists ian trust the scripture i
remember people in three retreat
really mentioned rirs retreats making
comments regardless my in Pomeroy is in
the form room my guy smartphone it's
idling on his way pulled off but unless
you have a valid perception of that ABBA
it has to be taken about what so long
mr. Beswick he said we believe that even
the state of Nirvana
sips that suit and Nirvana even the
state of Nirvana substance dentists no
mames any of you who could be China
stock height is room indeed home on the
island mention Alice we just don't have
the seeds to my life stop does short
experience for me a cell and so these
two truths these it's five are high are
we you know are we in a sense stuck in
the conventional intellectual
perceptions of yeah us intellect at
least which then is on to intellectually
our highest galilea heights violation I
get the city some interactively unholy
bending ourselves not say but rather
we're not doing this that's debate on
their side accounts on our phones and
when we study emptiness and esteem one
thing Geshe Michael - along the
qualities are salmon bass fell over on
Ashland Anita and her you know in my
invaded upon where and that's a
remarkable gift that's the side is a
paella take what he feel decoys sustain
the steal amok like side a complier
slimmer than this path we are doing then
be at the sky he wished for she were on
the right track dancin we often make and
that's where the laboratory of life
kicks in and we begin we have to
remember this by maybe three to five
thousand times a day on thrive is a
thousand mile um time but there is this
name envy accessibility right basically
it's almost as if like sometimes we have
to do this like you know you know it's a
it's it's just like going to the Hilton
gym right it's this V in in in in in
some hunting baby so kid
oh yeah yeah yeah
charge me it's better than most
neutralizing if it's negative we're
trying to understand not to have the
overwhelming emotion that's charging the
Commission a bad name in understating
everyone's comments early that's what no
I need done be admitted to consider
light if we could really understand the
pen about the conditions and the seeds
that we have to plant in order to
actually initiative directive our name
in Conan a couple of you asked me about
today that's why - on defrocked then we
have some really foundational launchpad
that happy a Berkeley and sprung bred
for meat really not such a cliche sleep
I now weigh not the Cindy trait meaning
of deviate hog stools you know I I
became a news junkie recently for course
finishing a gnostic charity board
station called an NPR which is so what
not having my hit of news you know like
when I'm not listening to anything tag
minded nicely she buys in the house
possibly like I need to hear its mostest
her latest buzz on what's going on in
the trumpets that it's just pure first
it lets your almost gossip right that's
almost like I call it know the ultimate
reality show actually a reality show is
going on it's so fresh
since I'm lacking entertainment of it
leave it in the Hydra is my gift
I fooled myself into thinking you stab
me since Ryan Kelly going on my skate
then vertically for entertain by abiding
by sound bites that are very dramatic
and very by decent Romar's list and you
know maybe my test today will be when
I'm starting to drive to Phoenix you
know so this is vs. minus 20db tiny me
know so first when guys are getting
stimulated by some video it's rain free
car wash
you sign video and coke oh my neck cost
blows out automation guys Diamond
Mountain is kind of beautiful diamond is
so sure corny OD on its assign a
commissioner say confess me internet in
the reduction is
there to debate or found the internet
Sookie no dating and sukham
retreat so drag listen when you mock
child me on sorry great a complete on
off the internet you know when you see
the direct perception of emptiness for
20 minutes direct even among the
lightest suits 1 Sigma know everything
you've done up to the point of seeing a
penis has contributed to that direct
perception via naming doesn't lead mom
and guitar afina are by keeping an
accounting book in how many are very
kind of hiding spoon be fill estimate
appear every fill astonish the order to
or experiencing I don't I'm personally
saying this we're not experiencing
radical change in our practice the most
common something that I think you see it
respect the stuff enemies knew about
Musa from then upon and the honesty of
five days of joy
[Music]
you know deeper in my life - I'm aware
see flecks in wood no less than one
ounce vanished on them no less six
target honestly that's the way the 15
minutes
[Music]
this seemed Ronan sister of Kibaki
non-silicon yoga it's so esoteric
strange wanting to see a one-component
did she understand cast but if you have
the inner event
it's you're on these two on deck
you are on the path to be stopped and a
lot of people until alert are kind of
tuning into the six flavors event and
you know listen to that that that
teaches and sweat under practices do you
it's a beautiful ocean and we and I say
to remind us
Kish Mehcad easily ahead Allen Allen
easy motion for this week's miss you
know fancy but from town and prosavana
logic the law had to first in on her and
her to gain a different effect then go
on the cushion and done last minute
that's done in the class just now so
they get define the class even doing a
meditation if that's your evil me go the
suitors bill looking to fill my for sue
headless men so if you know spend 40
minutes combat blots with nice exact
word get kids like you know a my my
thing is where is me is mine Boise
that's a great man annotation as a
nickel sentimentality on something
give yourself patients with its Aggie
dueling media scanning hearts feel it in
different at the equal level divorce
concentration concentration and
character constant what solidly ahead
field what's the other side resistor and
Allah said that is a reserved emptiness
what's on the head the flip side is the
undecided a civil answer yeah
interdependence or dependent origination
I'll ping against him what a king said
to get up yet
we have to learn karma you're missing
the common interest in the realization
of conscience with two Japheth the full
the full package this to something but
kids higher understanding from their
head we're gonna do something later how
many of you have not heard the two
husbands Experian and accurate met this
man each get one
oh my god you all have do you have to
solution be hey I think we should still
do stinking osorno starts tomorrow we
she's still doing this organist yeah not
yet not yet okay I'll get ready in a
minute
when I heard it does you know top singer
came at a retreat I thought it was a
stroke of genius justice blitz this is
remarkable
it just put everything into perspective
we were also in a teaching in Beijing at
the Beijing opera house they were on the
stage scholarship incredible one of them
was like this company and you were
trying to and it was just so abstract
and then guess you Michael God taught
the two husbands in the kids are a man
and a kick to the audience or twenty and
other people up publicly fund I just
remember the faces amazing for us and it
was so beautiful sort of moment
beautiful transmit the dark for salmon
in the bank amazing I you know I you
have to have first merit query good this
it's like you have to have good energy
something like that from all sections
keeps on it the American Le Mickey
Chavez come and the hair Cindy
Commission salmon 400 put a little
chaotic scene right here sanely ahead
while they're being bets you know I'll
be since go out and have
his crime was customer Derek that they
got in labor
oh my god not see on the TV there's so
many people having dinner I still feel
alerted visitors sort of consider that
the other two planet planet or the phone
constantly worms that are informally you
know heavy winds at Diamond Mountain
come around to your cabinets and I hit
the common or the other day there was
beautiful those are the nice things they
come as in the good thing in some
languages to write coming in to execute
you know you know let's give the
equanimity let from Thomas if you really
whatever you pick so question enduring
tragic things yes but are you
it
mimin was so vase it wasn't for him and
and perfectly poverty people say that to
us right the Sun it's incredible that
guy he knew I was to see me was to see
at caboose T so it's not like in pretty
fast listen mister a mansion and public
life startled and the hardening and
mission of passing and holding you went
is a song so hard is so
or to get this the gist of this Navarre
essential to evil a mystic ripening
incident Beauty and limb but also being
innovated something so we said you know
I'm gay suck an hour danced on the park
is really ridiculous including the
preliminary preliminary assess for
parents when it is shown here amongst in
this award
you know those can be considered
warm-ups but they're also from our
capitalist your fastest and citizen
epoxy serving other people stone gene in
the system and this is the sis this goes
with medication this is schism a minute
that's shown how do you serve we being
stunning fine that hinders the perfect
place to Suffolk the fiction is a great
I always think of carnivores
I don't know in my early days doing
thugs my company is an organization that
goes to people who can't cook for
themselves and it was really beautiful
massage people all I cared for the
[Music]
legacy
in Estonia you know hygienic orders
because there come with us can't get
fistula and so that was always a
beautiful finish I see I didn't have
toured together to detect fish thinkers
have wound above it opens you into this
firsthand land but most of you have that
it's like your service it's the ants
adenine Melissa no matter what can you
Oliver have fun yes my name's
it's just for life you love reading
beautiful chair and feel a my obsession
is summon seeds for enabling its
excellent both mental and physical
better guests together serving and get
you Michael just we should in New York
he saved my butt and I I was really
looking for a Spanish is about teaching
dishonest in all these
seductive things came
[Music]
okay anyway he he did right this is
comic health of the skin I definitely
shift my life with him said she forced
him and I never need to show and I was
grateful for dunk city supporters and
all of you are play finish yeah please
don't accuse we work very well in the
Steven over this Mandarin rituals in New
York against and that basically means
rituals in the urge honestly one of the
most beautiful struggling but paying
building interesting st. and New York
City in my place this market again a
photo ago become and Steven thank you
thanks
to finish it as well Mays longer so
maybe in three usually
honestly daddy and I are lovely and if
remotely she do a gig at this region and
gig in like you will money man is he
okay yeah okay
study study study and learn and learn on
them you gotta keep studying most vets
never miss this let the land on the
cysteine oh my fear
let's do the two husbands that's the
same another chemo so we're gonna teach
you to husband David nice to em top
English students come to college
demanda Sirach Peter betta maybe not
save me CJ yeah Maria come Maria so
Jenny's my kitchen this minute king de
Lucas my kids okay smile x-men Kint
okay we set it up this way I'm the
system's been in the oven liberating new
woman of the 21st century before headin
oil for him to be systematic
yeah you know being liberated women
Safina
and I cook a full 20 hours full Atlantic
student and so that's my life I'm
exhausted there's been a shift the set
up today is that us that the to the
office relates an itch bit because we
haven't quite sure I say okay obviously
brand new client could change the horses
for criminal Nouriel 20 hoon de datos
ready show today no chest then this yes
okay esta lección Martin I want you to
listen place its away take the Gibson
lived over so mommy
mama to be at the office need to be
dressed to be ready for specifics I
promise here for spoil your homework is
going to be done house thing good fit
Excel right good okay all right
okay so you know I make husband you know
I make the husband today even I made his
dinner there's that everything's cool is
is full of I wake up its 6:00 or 5:30
they're having a pillow fight - how many
boys what are you doing king of Oz
mastiha what are you doing what's my
told you oh my god got this very high
why do I get to work we get love the
presentation at the skillet though I
thought go to the store have a beautiful
I'd go shopping and I drank a coffee
Bhagyam anything in the house I pretty
much ready to see him forever Sonia to
say never so good to know now this years
and I just want to hug him hi honey
hello evening he gets to watch system
what what did you say my sister insect
to presume I'm stupid
he's been tone I didn't do anything have
missed your calling me stupid I just
want
you're coming with the new name among ah
miss tomb it's not my fault it's nice my
fella
I didn't do anything I was born
evolution unlit man I'm a man of many
men and Kingdom why did that happen is
perceived what was the point a sort of
bunks
they came out of nowhere demichev skip
common why do you do that to me Oh
master has made me a man literally to
list them my fault snitch man is short
so what just happened my sister Ida
Perseid three main things happened
writing is in business to assume is from
distance right the human in a creature
which husband will hire mice is for men
and salmon get coxswain aldis these are
the DISA yeah
Maria is she's my real husband I miss
miss Mia which husband is this well has
this it's not my fault husband assured
dear mom it's not my fault this is nice
man assured to God
husband number two not mine that's very
nice initial and assured a mine in the
common well no that's how my real
husband got into the kitchen
sois minh the exam i I called them
stupid caps it don't get any Holliman
leveland a month actually what resulting
right dependent origination up against a
on activate let's do some one main Smith
selenium and number number 2000 no Matt
same CY no me yeah this was me coming
this way he say
fundamentally I can't deny my suggestion
so what is that called
holy Nancy does well there's a word
called the Stockton but what the field
is gotcha gotcha gotcha I'm sure it's
one of your 21 miss from here thus got
chastised in dismay I remember that
honestly this is thing for them Leah
hudley ass that's right a.m. but never
him to me existence never having existed
and will never really exist in but we
put that in there because washed and his
name on the team of a home yeah because
we're hardwired well yeah - Edison
missing the point again magnetic a
subject to globe the stable consistent
this is a certificate and that happens
to the specific as many times so Felix
we're hardwired the missing of take this
out on Kilauea Minnetonka kinder okay I
have five so to wrap it up I'm summon
suffice is a PhD that's is clear that's
this is the sculpture let's see if we're
sure the class has shown on them at the
classify attic same I think that's about
the system was missing that's a question
anyone
yes yeah okay I really like how during
the luxury you said realities for some
somehow this really kind of struck me to
see this reality is deceptive let's deal
as five same yes I see disability says
listen health letter love yes
we could call it all pervasive they can
the Alistar thing in the silicon we
always come here missing email message
remittance summon out this seeds until
it being pushed into your next life with
you meet own citizen exist litigation
where else but missing Indian Christ
love when we're born when they get born
automatically automatically already in
this is awesome just less you have the
host attained an extraordinary also at
least a gangrenous latencies are really
by your decision 10-inch I don't vidacup
one random Underland so healthy but gets
wound and set on sailing layer device to
see in a crucible sees us at assistant
but you're here you salute this year
you've done some serious words it does
is perceived it slow - mister fortunate
for own business as the is wrong
with image defense itself anointing this
is good as is the power boost to
business okay okay
I guess we'll do the first double your
mom to skip it just one word
[Music]
punishing me
I grew corn on the same light to partial
Eden Wood aradhna mandala come the
attire
DK vocal tsunami a shirt socks auction
tsunami I should let your way dump our
corny little partial to thank you so
much Phil headland bag
[Applause]
[Music]